blueoceanstrategy.com 2019-11-04

# Privacy | Blue Ocean Strategy

Blue Ocean Strategy (“BOS”) adheres to the following policies concerning the information BOS collects from users of this website (the “Website”).

**BOS Does Not Sell, Share or Distribute Your Contact Information**

While using this Website, you may choose to submit personal information through on-line forms. BOS and its affiliated entities (“Affiliates”) will use this information to process your requests, but we will not intentionally sell, share, or distribute your personal information to third parties, except as required by applicable law. BOS and its Affiliates may also store this information for purposes of communicating with you and for the statistical purposes described below.

**Statistical Logs Kept**

In addition to any information you may affirmatively provide to BOS through on-line forms or otherwise, the Website is programmed to collect data about visitor traffic to the Web Site. BOS does not attempt to personally identify visitors to the Website. Instead we collect data to analyze in the aggregate to determine trends and improve our site. The following are some examples of the types of data we routinely collect:

• Internet address of computer  
• Browser type  
• Referring web page  
• Date, time & duration of visit

As part of the registration process for our e-newsletter, we collect personal information. We use that information to send you the newsletters and information you’ve signed up for; to contact you if we need to obtain or provide additional information; to check our records are correct and to check if you’re satisfied and get your feedback. We don’t rent or trade email lists with other organisations and businesses.

We use a third-party provider, MailChimp, to deliver our newsletter. We gather statistics around email opening and clicks using industry standard technologies to help us monitor and improve our e-newsletter. For more information, please see [MailChimp’s privacy notice](https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/). You can unsubscribe to general mailings at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any of our emails.

Under the General Data Protection Regulation (the “GDPR”), you have the right to access and amend any of your personal data that we hold. Simply email your request to **news(at)blueoceanstrategy(dot)com**. 

**Links**

Links to Other Websites and Search Results: The Website may contain links to websites operated by other parties. BOS provides these links to other websites as a convenience, and your use of these sites is at your own risk. The linked sites are not under the control of BOS and BOS is not responsible for the content available on these third party sites. Such links do not imply endorsement of information or material on any other site and the BOS disclaims all liability with regard to your access to, use of or transactions with such linked websites. You acknowledge and agree that BOS shall not be responsible or liable, directly or indirectly, for any damage, loss or other claim caused or alleged to be caused by or in connection with, access to, use of or reliance on any content available on or through any other site or resource.

Links to the Website: You may link another website to the Website subject to the following linking policy: (i) the appearance, position and other aspects of any link may not be such as to damage or dilute the reputation of BOS or the Website; (ii) the appearance, position and other attributes of the link may not create the false appearance that your site, business, organization or entity is sponsored by, affiliated with, or associated with BOS or the Website; (iii) when selected by a user, the link must display the Website on fullscreen and within a “frame” on the linking website; and (iv) BOS reserves the right to revoke its consent to the link at any time and in its sole discretion.

The foregoing policies are subject to change. We encourage you to check back for updates from time to time. If you have additional questions about this privacy statement, we invite you to contact:

**admin(at)blueoceanstrategy(dot)com**

Last Updated: May 2018  
Effective Date: October 1st 2012
